UNITE Accounting Department File on Contractors 6000/052
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Accounting Department File on Contractors
1957-2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
6000/052
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Records.
This collection contains a significant amount of material from ILGWU.
7130136
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, February 08, 2011
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000 AV: UNITE Audio-Visual Collection 6000 G: UNITE Posters 6000 MB: UNITE Memorabilia 6000 P: UNITE Photographs 6000 PUBS: UNITE Publications 6000/044 P: UNITE Photographs
Clothing workers--Labor unions--United States; Textile workers--Labor unions--United States; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees. Accounting Dept.; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization)
7130136
- A, 1964-2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- B, 1979-2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- C, 1962-2002 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- D, 1984-2002 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- E, 1964-2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- G, 1986-2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- H, 1978-2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- I, 1970-2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- J, 1972-2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- K, 1969-2002 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- L, 1972-2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- M, 1984-1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- N, 1987-2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- O, 1972-1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- P, 1957-2002 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- R, 1960-2002 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- S, 1964-2002 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- T, 1979-2002 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- V, 1974-2002 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- W, 1973-2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Chinese Contractor: Numbers, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Chinese Contractor: A, 1994-2002 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Chinese Contractor: B, 1998-2003 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Chinese Contractor: C, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Chinese Contractor: D, 1996-2002 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Chinese Contractor: E, 1988-2003 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Chinese Contractor: F, 1997-2002 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Chinese Contractor: G, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Chinese Contractor: H, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Chinese Contractor: I, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Chinese Contractor: J, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Chinese Contractor: K, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Chinese Contractor: L, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Chinese Contractor: M, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Chinese Contractor: N, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Chinese Contractor: O, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Chinese Contractor: P, 1994-2003 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Chinese Contractor: Q, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Chinese Contractor: R, 1990-2003 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Chinese Contractor: S, 1995-2003 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Chinese Contractor: T, 1982-2003 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Chinese Contractor: U, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Chinese Contractor: V, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Chinese Contractor: W, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Chinese Contractor: XYZ, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 45)